ELLI RAYNAI

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+1 647 996 7420

elli@elliraynai.com

636 Danforth Ave, Toronto, M4K1R3

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/

elliraynai.com

github.com/eraynai

PROFILE

I am a full stack developer with a background in user experience design. My coding journey began with building interactive and engaging experiences in VR/AR. From there I began experimenting with the web, and fell in love with development. I have a passion for building applications and working collaboratively in a team to make the best possible product.

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

React

Express

NodeJS

MongoDB

Vue

Django

PostgreSQL

Python

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

EDUCATION

Software Engineering Immersive General Assembly

May 2021 - August 2021

Interaction Design and Development George Brown College

September 2018 - April 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Armstrong Partnership | November 2021 - Present

- Converted PSD files into pixel perfect HTML emails
- Strategized solutions for mobile responsive design
- QA tested emails using software and mobile devices
- Built static websites and implemented interactive features using vanilla JavaScript

Creative Technologist Intern

No Fixed Address | January 2021 - April 2021

- Sole frontend developer on a campaign for a client utilizing the Vue.js framework
- Consistently performed well under pressure amid tight time constraints and had to learn new development skills during the project
- Conducted market research on different types of technologies that could be utilized by clients

AR Designer

Snap | October 2020 - December 2020

- Participated in the Snap AR residency based on the my pitch for a machine learning experience called 'Nourish'
- Responsible for creative direction, user flows, concept designs, motion capture animation for 3D models, and programming interactions in JavaScript

Interaction Designer

Cream Productions | May 2020 - August 2020

- Designed and delivered a coherent vision for a casual VR game
- Conducted user interviews, competitive landscape analysis, and personas
- Built the game storyline, mechanics, and level design in collaboration with the development team